Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame, but the chats on fire can't
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot flashing on cam chat
losing their minds michael getting domed alex taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every
night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond
flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yo all facts yo
Not tonight Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls we pretend to play
We're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness, buckle up tight
Boobs flashing on cam, chat losing their minds
Michael getting gong to Alex taking flight
It's wild, it's wrong and we do it every night
Paige got him simping hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirting hard, let the girls react
It's a freak show, party, no filter, all facts
Yeah, all facts
You know the vibe.
Shit, okay. Hey guys, what's up? I'm trying to help me fix it
Person, I don't know. Can you fix it? Maybe I need to do this one. Let's try this
Let's take it.
I'm trying something new here.
Yeah, let's see if this works.
Ah, okay.
Now try it.
Try this one.
I have other ones to put into.
I need to fix it. I don't know. It's not working perfect. Okay. Well, forget about that for now.
Forget about that. Just ignore that right now. How are you? Okay, so I have some surprises.
Okay, it was a weird day. Like today, I returned like my readers because the readers were like,
you know, the ones I just got, they were like, they're like too blurry. Like I like my other
ones, like my Dalmer ones are perfect. Like I can see good in these, like no matter what,
So there were three pairs right I got with that but when I like gathered them up when I returned to Whole Foods and like went
Into my bit there's like some stuff went to the store. I came home and I was like and I like looked and then I saw
these
Now I was like what I was like what why do I still have a pair of glasses?
So I accidentally
Have a pair of dark glasses that look kind of like this and I put these are glasses in with the three of them and return those
Okay, so I went back
And she already put the fucking thing in some seal box and it's over that they're gone
but I
Haven't I have these I mean they're so powerful. They're powerful. They're good. I can see the text. It's fine
And I have them. I did like those glasses
But I haven't for a few years and so no well. Oh, well, okay. I
Have one more thing to grab. We'll be right back
Okay, I'm back. Okay. Let me just I mean, I can't show one of the things because I have some beauty in it
I got a toy told the chat. Okay, but anyway, I'll pop it. I'll put some cell phone
Okay, I can't show that one. Okay
Shit
Okay, I
Can show you I can show you a little bit. I'm gonna save the rest for like, you know see me some on some other time
I'll show it hold on, but I want to show spunky and everybody I was working. I do it. I was working on like some cards
Oh shit, hon
Okay, are you all there?
Hi guys
Is everything good? I took this to Thursday. Oh, no, I took you to Thursday. Why didn't I says Tuesday?
Is it
Book shit. Is there anything good? Okay. Yeah, so spunky. Are you there? I made I made the lovers card
I want to show you the lovers card. I mean, it's a guy that spent like a long time on them
It's not just like oh, okay, you want to see okay?
So I still need to take I I'll get your picture and I'll make it look more like you but these are still prototypes
I'm still working on it. Okay, so
I mean, so I was like first I was like, yeah, dude do it like this and then
It's hard to look at the, it's hard to see, it's hard to see, hold on, let me see, let's go there here.
Okay, well, I'll just take a risk, hold on, hold on, let me put, shit, I can't.
Okay, I see, I see.
Did I do it? Okay, hold on one second. Oh yeah, so this at file for the library.
Okay, and I have too many pictures, so I need to delete something. Okay, delete that.
Yeah, this is getting a little ridiculous. I know. Okay, you got to show it. Okay, I'm going to show
you. Let's take it. So there's a few things came out. Okay, I think I got them all.
Okay, so here's what I did first.
I was like, you know, I had some idea.
Oh, it didn't do this first.
I can't show the first one
because there's too much nudity in it.
But here's the first one, okay.
So there we go.
We got a lover that says,
at your side, I feel divinely connected.
Okay, so that's one of the things.
That's the first idea.
Then, with this one.
Now I was like, I want it in a more realistic,
like beautiful style.
We got this
So that's what we have right now, so that's a working one spunky. I don't know I need a little more can use a little work
Okay, what does it say in the garden of? Hold on
Says the garden of choices temptation and guidance are two sides of the same coin choose with your heart, but keep your eyes open, okay?
So that's that.
OK, now I can see what I was looking at.
OK, one, two, OK.
OK, also, I have some other ones.
Oh my god, they're really funny.
I just need to delete a few of these so I can bring them back.
OK, give me one second.
OK, here we go.
Okay, you might laugh at these ones. So I did a wheel of fortune to you. Okay, go to the library
Okay, got this. Okay
So, okay, so we'll fortune. I just got I was like, okay, well, let me do the wheel of fortune with you know
Somebody I know somebody that probably you know everyone tells me I'd my let's talk about them anymore
I know they're they can be Ilya but it's like personal chat GPU was like no
I'm not doing that and then I was like, okay, just put big leaves on them and then it was like
I'm an angel I am you love it. Okay. Good. Good. I think that was I came out cute
I'm gonna make it look more like you okay, but I think it came out really cute
Okay, so I was like so so the other one was the wheel fortune. I was like well
I'm gonna put somebody I think I think you guys might know who it is. Okay, let's just figure out
So, but I had to do a few times to like get the right thing. I think so this was the first
That goes deleted on this one. It's deleted shit
Oh shit, okay. Well, there's one of them. Okay, but I had it twice. Okay, so there's one of them
They're really excited. Okay, I put the wrong one up. Okay one second
Okay, okay, hold on I fit the wrong one up. Okay, so I just delete that one. Oh shit. Oh, oh
Have okay, so the first one that came up for that you guys know who it is
It didn't really good job of them actually hold on you might not know who it is not
It's not somebody you might know hold on but here's here's what looks like okay, so look what came up
So first I came up with this one
Right here
Okay, real fortune, okay
So it came out with a wheel fortune. Okay, I think guys by the way, I'm like I'm like discussing all these ideas and stuff
Like it's a very like detail that I've been through a lot of stuff with this. Okay, so that was the first one
Okay, then I was like, okay. Well can make them like, you know
I just need to be a little bit different, I know.
I guess, is this the one I picked?
I'm not sure.
But then I said, do we make it different?
Okay, then I came up with that one.
Fortune turns like a wheel, some are up, others are down.
Okay, there's one.
But then I was like, make him look excited.
And so then we did that one.
Oh, we look really excited, right?
Fortune has greatly ever-changing, ever-fascinating.
Okay, finally, I think I came up with this one.
Hold on, that's the first one, hold on.
One, two, three, hold on.
Okay, well, I don't know. Anyway, I think this I think that this is supposed to be the this is not that one
I think this one's supposed to be like the this one's a beauty what I choose. I don't know or maybe this one
This one looks pretty good, too
Okay, I gotta like that one too. Okay
Okay, and then I have a tower. I'll show the tower too. Why okay, here's a tower I have
My kind of a little esoteric, I don't know if you like that one. What do you think is that too controversial guys?
Oh, it's not Elisa. It's Emma. It's Emma Leviathan. Elisa will be on a car. Oh, she's gonna be a queen
But yeah, at least she'll be on a car, but uh, yeah, it's Emma Leviathan. I don't know if you saw. Yeah
This is that this what I mean this one to you. I was like it was supposed to be me and beta
But it's like I put it. I don't know if it looks like me. I might put you know
Hello
I'm gonna get I'm gonna be on a watch list up. Oh, well, I don't know if it's you guys the chat GPT made this
Okay, I did I mean that I I told her what to make but it's like it did it
Just friend. Oh, yeah, Fred. Yeah, Fred is gonna be mad. Oh my god. Oh my god. It looks like her
What is the tower? No, it doesn't Radimus. I that wasn't this is the tower, but the other one was a wheel of fortune
Okay, you have to pay attention a little bit. Okay. The other one was wheel of fortune not the tower
See it says wheel of fortune
That's somebody I know right
She's not just some big-titted goth girls Emma. Okay. She's a Satan's actual ex-wife
Anyway, not that kind of looks like Bob Larson or something like not really me the tower is good. You like that one
Yeah, Fred. Are you there? Fred is gonna pop up
The guys they're looking good, huh? They're pretty good. Hey spunky. You're having a me day. You're getting a tattoo. Yay
I'm and I'm nasty fucking nickel. Oh, are you saying that?
It means that
Maybe the Wheel of Fortune is like I'm thinking like a game show right was that to do with a big TV?
They're all explain it to so, you know a sucky bus
Like she's a sucky bitch, right? She's a sucky. She looks oh, they can't we just say you oh high priestess on your arm
Oh my gosh, that's awesome. I these maybe I'll maybe I'll remake you as a high priestess. Bunky. I'll maybe I might do that
You really you know Emma I'm really um
Thought you know goes along with high priestess too and she even got attached you on her leg of high priestess
They showed me the pic. I can't wait to see she can suck your bis okay the cigars your cock, but mine isn't half the length
Yeah, it's some kind of suck you the spell. I don't know. I didn't mean I didn't even like either spaghetti and still
Don't love but well, I don't know. I
Don't know. I think she's helping for the other car. Maybe she'll be flatter
Maybe she'll I don't know. Hopefully she'll sue me for like, you know, whatever
I think I don't think it's like any kind of like bad bad thing
Trisha says thank you. Oh awesome. Thank you
Yeah, I think Emma's very beautiful and maybe I don't know. It's like, you know, and you know my type
It's like, you know, Beda, you know, Alisa, Emma, you know, Beda too. I mean, Beda is more like, you know, friend,
friend energy, but I'm talking about like, you know, he's like
Middle of the night scares me to the death. Like, it's like, yeah, it's so cute. It's you thought I was gay
Yeah, I'm gay, but it's like I'm a very complicated person though because I do like succubus. Obviously in my tattoo
This is my first tattoo. I don't know if you ever see it
Well, there you can see
No, if you saw it too good
Anyway
Who um
But yeah, I don't know I don't know but I hope you like it
Yeah, it's monkey awesome a hole is always well, you know, it's like it's kind of like
Do I imagine would I imagine like?
It's it's like basically like a Lisa with like Andy dick. It's like
Hey, we're married. It's like really cute, but it's like they're not their course night
They're not really your game. It didn't mind a bit of this new shoe. I
Know I'm only dated one person. It was a woman, right?
Shit so this is like a little bit I just so it was like scraping the pipe and it's like has no dry tobacco
So it's not burning. Okay
Guys, it's gonna be really cool deck though
I'm gonna leave a few cards open for like people to bid on because I'm gonna do a Kickstarter for it
And so it's like one of the Kickstarter things like one of the premium offers is gonna be like, you know
It'll be for at least 300 to 500 dollars. It will be like, you know, I have a custom
card either you can maybe I'll have either like you design it or I'll just put your likeness in it or
something and you can have a card in the deck it's gonna be very awesome other stuff too I'll have some
merch made off some special prints of like maybe I'll print of every card and that'd be awesome because
then we are not every card but maybe just some majors so we can have at least 22 of those as you
know sponsored or stuff and then I'll be able to with that if I make the hmm how much do I want to
Um, I think I would probably want to raise for these cards at least
Two to three thousand dollars. Okay
Um, because it will talk to take it probably 1500 dollars to print them plus, you know
That's gonna be more more than that, you know, but for 100 decks
Yeah
But they're gonna be awesome though. I'm not a carpet. I never um, I find you I never ate the carpet
I just put my fingers um in the carpet no rug
Radamus what are you saying? I go down. No, I never did. She she offered but then she was on her period at the time
So I said no, but I don't know. It was very weird. I was 33 years old. It's a weird year
Stickers or shirts with the car perch it on yeah
I'll get some stickers, I'll get some of my favorite cards.
I have, I mean, the cards, they're just in development.
So it's like, I'm just like testing, like,
oh, how will this look, how will this look?
I'm thinking of ideas.
I'm gonna make it them unified.
They're gonna be look really unified at the end, right?
They're gonna be like all like,
oh, this is like the same artist of these or whatever, right?
That's why I'm trying to get the the cartoon like I'm trying to do cartoon style
But then it came out to cartoony and so I like the how detailed this is it came out so beautiful
Like I think this is like my favorite card so far like how beautifully detailed it
I love if they look like this because it's like the so
detailed and realistic and
Yeah, I was like, you know, put big leaves and like a seashell bikini and as I said put an S and a J on the tree
Do you see that detail spanky or spunky? It says S and S plus J
And so it's like kind of like a nod to you. You see it. Okay. You see it
So and I like them I like them I like the the quote we came up with too so
This is a little preview how things are going. It's gonna be really cool though. You love it
Yeah, and it's gonna I'm gonna do those little details like on I'm trying to do every card
I put a little nod to the person on it and
Yeah, because it's like, you know, you guys are my life. I love you guys and I yeah
So you're every part of it like I think everyone's pretty much
We're part of the deck even though it's probably gonna be one card the world and I'll just put like everybody on it
Like it's gonna be maybe it'll be like really like it'd be like the charge of pepper lonely hearts album or something or it's like
You know, oh look at this person and then in 20 years from now
We're all famous and they're like, oh there there was in this guy's project before too
Like because I think a lot of a lot of you are destined for like if you haven't found it already you're destined for some greatness, right?
Fame fortune or or otherwise, right?
Hopefully emphasis on the fame and fortune and so
Guys, I'm also setting up the power chat
So I will probably have some like, you know, I'll do some weekly shows like I'll probably do a bit
Maybe like two or three shows a week that are just gonna be
Like that through either power chat. This is especially when I get my computer like this month
It'll be this month. I'll get it but and so then I'll be able to put the power chat more into like use
but then I'll have so I'll have like a
And I even can if I'm gonna get the computer I can still do stream yard on it
I just have to like share the screen with the power chats. Oh, it's okay. It'll be more complicated, but
That'll allow some TTS donations and like message to be read out loud with a with a I'm not breaking up with you at all
No, no, no, no, what do you mean breaking up with you? I'm we're just getting started in this relationship
I'm bringing more people into it
I'm bringing like you know
I am on tick-tock and it's like tick-tock is more of the tarot people
but also I mean people there that when I come over here too and I really do like to have more people with
Interested in tarot and stuff over here. I guess I kind of mix it up
Cuz sometimes there's days where is that people are not I don't even ask me for reading and stuff
And that's like I really do want that to be bigger part of the show and it's my fault. I need to put it out there more
right
Oh
You're poking me. Okay
It'll be in your 50s and 30 years. Yeah, but I'm a yeah people thought oh, you know, and it's like I should be
Focus like a hundred percent on YouTube. And so it is like a little bit of like I
Just don't want to be too much for you guys. I don't want it to be I don't want to crack burn out on it
I'm just having panels and stuff like that. And I want to also have the you know my me
I'll be out there and also I like to talk. I do like to talk
There's a lot of you guys there. I do like to hit on guys and
Even the straight guys, I don't think that really any of mine did me hitting on them
I give gifts and stuff
Uh-oh
You're gonna make a movie about psyche and Jimmy in a romance style movie. However, Hoover crimp meets a terribly terribly lover
Wow, I actually when I first started on YouTube
I was going to panels and I went to this at first I played this I went to the black panels
It was called the the B sector or like the most three sector or the
And those things right was black sector. And so the first thing I did was a plate hood jeopardy
And it was really fun, and I didn't win, of course, I was like, but I did okay. I got some points
And I was like this weird white guy that's already told me Jeffrey Dahmer there
But I think one of the second shows I went on what's called the good pussy show
She's really cool. You can look it up the good pussy show
She does open panels and stuff, but it's a little crazy.
It's like, you know, the black open panels are a little bit different.
They're like kind of like mine, but even crazier.
And even it's kind of like, like, imagine just if Birdo was just like everybody on the panel.
That's how it is.
Screaming and not that's how it's like it's like burdo is like every cure. So that's how that's what I was trained on
You know, so burdo is like nothing. It's like yeah, whatever like nothing
Well, I think Jimmy would probably be the bottom. I'm just guessing but listen don't tell him that okay anyway, so
I did this with the one of the first people I met. There was this a crypt from Texas and then I was like
Oh, I was like hitting on him and then he's a black crypt and he started but he actually wears like red and blue bandanas
very confusing and
Blue and red the good pussy show. Yeah, I think you have to go P you at and put the s and there's like dollar signs
I'll see if I can find it real quick. Hold on. I'll show you
Oh shit
Here I found her I found her
That's your name your show. Yeah, I know her actually she called good pussy 45 now
But I don't have a cute 45s of all but let me I'll put it here's her link you guys can I say hi to her. Oh
Shit just lost it home
Okay, oh yeah, I think I got it here
So that's you can say her name is her name is um, sco mysterious or something like that. Okay, so she's good to see 45
She's really nice and she actually it was like one of those people that's like, hey
She's like, you know, you know all she actually made all her all people that became members for like 99 cents
She made a mods and stuff and let them promote her promote their shows and she was like
Oh, yeah, everyone like streamed my show at the same time and I said she was really nice
I just like, you know, it's kind of like they call me sorry coming call me Jeffrey and then it's like
Then it's like I got kind of kind of controversial and I like oh shit. I stopped going over there, but
Yeah, I kind of just cleaning my pipe a little bit
Resin out of here
So that's pretty interesting. How are you guys today? It's a nice Tuesday
I got the rest of the week ahead of us, but I got a couple drinks Yuri Crow
You know what a Mexican war like war cry sounds like cacao or something like that
Whoo
You're pretty good. Okay good. I'm pretty good, too. I
I'm in like today. I've been researching it like on
You know what kind of computer I want to get
Consider a lot like I was looking at like you know my chat GPT's like oh you're gonna
I was like I just want a computer that can play VR and stuff. I have a VR headset
It's like oh, well you spent $1,000. I think it might be a couple years behind or something like that
Because I think I can probably get a good computer to call me Jeffrey like Jeffrey Epstein
Oh Jeffrey like Jeffrey Dahmer like my glasses, right?
And that was before even was wearing glasses
So they're wearing it way ahead of the time not Jeffrey Epstein Jeffrey Epstein looks more like what?
Anthony Bourdain and any more gray hair for Epstein
But he also he's a very typical Jewish look too, but I
Don't really believe in the whole Epstein. I think it's a style up
What do you think?
I do with the glasses. Yeah, I do and I like these glasses a lot
And so I mean I have now I have this pair too. This is my Oprah pair
I Oprah glasses, but I need to these I need to look on the screen close. I need to look this close
My eyes look really big at them. I kind of like these. I mean if I was to give it a pair
I'd either kind of like the leopard or tortoise shell print. I mean I kind of like them
They're kind of cool
I mean the other glasses were Kanye West Northwest glasses had them for several years
I mean they were there's all the everything I rubbed off of them. They were kind of like either cool, but I
Can get a pair of glass for like 10 bucks?
So anyway, tell you just your rap I L, but I like these ones
Well, I'm Radamus Prime. I don't I don't know about that. I know it was called Epstein Island or it's called Little Saint James
I had this Venetian temple Venetian means Phoenicia means the pony means fake
If there's a Venetian temple anywhere, it's like oh, I know what that's about
It's giving you a little little hint that it's a fake story just a little hint. Okay, if you see stuff like
They also these things like seashells which used to be their money
Yeah, the ocean kingdom they're really into the maritime stuff like piracy pirates and
They were the first merchants and first people with the merchant language
So the first language is Phoenicia if you deny it means you're there well go ahead
I want to see I want to see the plane flight logs by me on the plane fight flight log right not on there
I'm under my alias, which is
PDD the third. I'm just kidding
Oh, God, these cigars, these are backwoods.
I think they were like, it's like they were rolled
in the backwoods by like some guy back there.
Could look at their up all playing part.
Not hitting, right?
It costs twice as much for one
that the Swisher's Suites cost for two at half right.
So this is like 250 for one.
Swisher's Suites were like 150 for two.
So I could buy like $5 would get me like,
three or six Swisher's Suites.
$5 got me two of these crappy,
These are these these suck look at this point point. Is it even light? Oh
Sorry, I don't like you. Oh
I'm gonna get accused of like crashing out again like I'm not really yeah
I'm not crashing okay, but guys are you liking the stuff on tick-tock too?
I'm actually able to animate some of my my stuff on tick-tock like I'm some of some of the
photos or cartoons and stuff. Oh if you
Spunky if you go to tick-tock
Look look at look I put the devil card up there and click on that devil picture on my page and it animates it into like a Disney cartoon
It's really funny. The first one I made was really weird and scary
Then I was like well animate it into it like an animate like a cartoon and then it made it really like
It hurts in the Disney characters. You can guys like you can go to my tiktok page and look at that if you want. I'm
psyche awakens
Tarot on tiktok. You have to put all the all the three words
Because yeah, I'm psyche awakens
No, I
That was my first account, but I forgot about it. So oh
I have a new logo to hold on I'll put the logo up
You guys like this one
Where is it there it is you like it
Now you can kind of read the name of the chat read the name at least right
Yeah, we're open here we go, of course open for you a ghost of course
Guys I do have readings open available
And for private in a private readings paid readings, you know, and like I said for members, you know
I would usually do like $25 for a half hour
For members if you'd like to book a reading, I'll give you like 45 minutes to an hour
You know, I'll go I'll go almost twice as long it depends on if you know if we there's information cut like more information coming out and
Guys if you want to book a reading and members will get 45 to an hour and non-members will get 30 minutes for it
Okay, I'll put my cash app up and just
if you're interested go ahead and hit my cash app and then I will schedule within the next 24 hours
we'll do the reading over the phone okay I think it's a good deal I think that if you do want a
longer reading and you haven't had a longer reading from me which you might not have because I do
short readings on this show okay there's there's an option for you to get a really good long
I appreciate that thank you, and then there's also if you ever do you want to send anything for like panel or
You know response from the panel or kicking people off the panel
There's a cash up same one on the bottom of the screen psyche awakens a dollar sign psyche awakens. So there you go
Hello
Yeah, what's up, ghost?
What's up, brother?
How's it going?
Good good. Hey, I'm gonna stop asking for readings because I didn't understand you had
People paying for readings. You know, that's a good idea
No, I mean I say I'm happy to do free readings
But it's like I will people now think that I just see these really short readings and I don't do short readings
I do long readings and detailed but on the show for free. I do a little bit shorter readings and
And if I get a donation, I'll pull more cards or if it's a member of poor more cards
But uh, but you can ask for I mean you can ask for me and you've also you know ghost you've contributed a lot to the show
I'm not gonna forget that. I'm gonna I'm gonna be able to get my computer this month
Thanks to you and you know, basically you've helped upgrade this show. I mean, you don't see it
You guys won't see it yet because I mean it's like I will take a little bit for everything to get worked out
but the computer will come this month and then I'll be able to
run the show up the computer stream it I'll get I'll get a mixing board I'll get
a sound effects board I'll get like a my microphone hooked up I'll get I'll be
able to share the screen and do some really cool stuff and I'll be able to
use the OBS and the power to be able to do so much stuff I'm not able to do
right now it'll just make it a new show hopefully in a good way
You know, I really hope you guys are enjoying the show. I'm gonna put I'm gonna post the link right now if
Ghost if you want it, I think you have a panel to go so you can you call this your panel if you'd like
And to keep it open or a little brother. Okay, maybe you can
Okay, well ghost is here, so he said it's open if you guys can like the
Stream and I'll pin the link send a little bit of money and to my voice like me if you don't mind
We're not asking for it, but if you want to donate, I mean feel free
Yeah, and I really appreciate anything. I didn't know it sometimes, you know, YouTube does pay out once a month
$2 goes a long ways brother, right?
And you know, and I appreciate every penny too and it's like in really
So I've gotten so like there's been so much so much that you guys have just done so much for me
So much like giving me like wonderful gifts and donations and this helped me out in so many ways
So I have a few cards for this for you ghost because you know, I think you have some haters, right?
So I just I just deck this is called haters exposed and it's called the yeah, it says the evil eye or
No, this is this is like not about you
This is about people that
are hating on you maybe you're aware maybe you're not okay let's go okay so i'll pull i mean uh
There's shuffling, there's a lot of cards in this deck.
It's a really cool deck.
I think you will enjoy this deck.
And it gives remedies as well as maybe some ideas
of what's happening.
Okay, so first we have, for ghosts,
we have this cedar, okay?
So cedar, so kind of tree.
So the cedar wood you might have a relation to it.
It says, fresh woodsy smell cleans a new home
of its old energies and unwanted spirits
while inviting fresh energetic vibes
and protecting the new occupants.
So if you are, yeah, if you have like a,
Look up like burning cedar or cedar incense or something like that. I think that would be good
You know as a kind of a way to clear out your the energy of your home and bring in some good energy
Close out mosquitoes and I don't like sucking mosquitoes
Perfect. Well, that's the cedar. We perfect. Okay. What else we got for ghosts
We got it says seek someone to perform or learn to do a hex braking ritual
And so you might want to like look into that if you are interested in like hex braking
i'd i can you know give you a little advice like a i would say for you
you know you broke your brother she's a little kind of something there
Right, I mean, yeah, but that's what I'm saying if you I mean or anybody anybody that does want to know how to break a hex or
Evil eye or something. There's a couple ways that I know that are very effective. One is a spiritual bath
You know say a psalm over it like Psalm 93 or something
Good like against enemies and stuff and the evil eye and then also you can smudge, right?
And also, I would like you how do you feel about this though? I think a little bath not so refresh night
After I say it and I'm not joking either. I said the power of Christ
Compels you or something therefore the power of Christ. What do you say? Sorry compels you
Exactly and I say you guys you got to say your name. That's what I repeat and I ain't hearing shit
Okay, well, it's like you can just read whatever you like over like a Psalm
Psalms are very magical you can say a part of Jesus or where whoever you believe in and
But also there's another like a kind of like a who-do kind of way to take care of any evil eye
Or negative energy is to rub an egg all over your body
Picture all the negative energy going inside that egg and then like but I would just like throw in the garbage disposal
Turn on my first defense man my first defense. I want me to be read my first defense is this you are debate myself
Not debate anyone. Mm-hmm. And then once we take it further than we can take it further, you know, I'm saying
You got it. So in the next card you got ghost is so this person that is
It better be a warrior. No, this is about this. I think the person that doesn't like you
It says they have a personality disorder and they don't know how to be. Oh
Well, I knew what that is. I ain't got much no name
So that might maybe and I'll pull a couple more just to because these might have remedies or ants only one more one more
Okay, one more the last one the last one is as it says Jupiter retrograde
Okay, so I wanna I want Leo card. Do you have any Leo cards or do you have to guess Leo is the Sun, right?
But so it's the Sun. I don't know if it's Leo card
Well, so it's a no it says the person causing also no first thing the person causing you negativities an earth sign
Okay, that's what it says and it also says Jupiter retrograde problems with making important life changes for future benefits of
Expansion abundance and prosperity so there might be a little bit a little bit of slowness
Maybe because Jupiter's in retrograde
Which means Jupiter's going the normal direction that it normally goes right?
And so that's gonna be a temporary thing.
And so maybe you're not necessarily cursed by someone,
maybe it's just like a bad astrological time.
And so I just considered those different things.
I would say burn that seed or whatever you mean.
Or maybe I'm just lying and like,
who's the top dog in your cards?
Who's the top dog besides lying?
Well, I would say Saturn. I would say I would say Saturn is like a very powerful planet because it has to do with the manifest
Yes rings. No Saturn steak. Yes, they guess rings
They're gonna last for like a couple of like fucking million years and they're gonna go away
Okay, well as I'll just say astrologically like the Sun is very interesting
The Sun is very powerful in astrology, of course
We know we know because like you know the Sun is about it's like everything revolves around the Sun
The Sun is about your identity and like your ego and stuff and it's also a fiery thing and so you know, it's very
You know out there in front of the center just like Aries and in the other fire
But I'm just talking with you psyche. I never I'm never gonna
And I don't mean to see you know, I don't mean no dish
I'm never gonna pay for like a one-on-one with you, but I'll pay to have no piano and I love though
Hey, I'm not gonna pay for no fuck it. Wait, whatever. Hey, whatever
But that's why there's a track man. It's okay get along
I agree. That's why I have both available. I have stuff for the panel. I have stuff for
readings. Whatever you guys would like. And there's also an Amazon wish list. And there's
other ways to support the show. I agree.
But I appreciate everything guys and it's like and guys. This is my best month on on YouTube and my first month
I've made
You know for four digits and how much I've made wow, let's fucking go
Yeah, so that's exciting for me and
And a lot of that is people that are on recurring memberships or in a lot of super chats and
Not to mention. I'm also, you know, people have sent me a cash app, which is not necessarily so I even made more
Factoring the cash apps, you know, I made it probably my best month in a long long long time. So
Wow, I'm happy. I'm really happy and like you can see like I kind of like
reacted to this by like I cleaned my house. I'm like
Stopped I got some stuff. I need I got everything organized. I'm like I have like all these ideas
Everything's going much better. So it's like it was such an encouragement goes
I don't know if you ever like we'll really know it really just meant a lot to me that you like
Because I was at a time where I was like, hey, I thought like everybody hated me pretty basically and then for you to come and like
Step in and really like an expression to me because we're not even like agree. I love a shit, but we get along
Right and that's great. I mean, that's like, you know, I think I'm like, you know
Different than a lot of people and like, you know, we're very different people
But if you can get along with people that are different than you if you can accept and you like differences rather than you
You think any difference exactly what I've done. That's exactly what I did. Yeah, I believe you you have you put your bunny
Where your mouth is too because people don't just like
If they put money behind something, it's like it kind of shows you they're not just like, you know fucking with you
It's like, you know, they're they're using some of their and energy, which is basically that you know, they're fuel
They're you know, they're their wealth to support to support you and so it's like, you know
It's almost like them supporting themselves in a certain way because it's like that they would only
get to something that, you know, that they liked or something on it. So I don't think maybe I truly hated me
But you know, I did see like Sean. What's his name? Sean James. I did tell you to open it up
Yeah, Sean, whatever. I did tell you to open it up. Let's open that up. Oh, yeah
Well, I'm saying to Tommy James like he's been on recently in my chat. It's like everything I say he's like, oh, you know
You don't know anything you're stupid. Let's run it
Now my knees are over there because here. I'll run it. Then I saw his then I saw one of his comments
And he's like we all hate you or we don't he said we don't like you and I just like who's so we don't like you like
How can I run it for anybody? Thank you. Yeah, Tommy. James if you're here you want to talk about who doesn't like me
Which made me think oh, nobody likes me, you know, because I'm sensitive to like
People I got you all right man. I know we can be sensitive. Let's run that
Was he not here I
Don't think he's here, but he said it yesterday. I put a lot. I happened a lot in the show
Yeah, I was going I was going through like, you know, you know
This some of my streams today that I must have like I must have been on for every day this year except for one day
There's one Monday. I did not stream
But I've been on every other day, at least for a little bit, and sometimes for 10, 12 or more hours.
And that's not plus I deleted so many streams that they'll be gone forever.
But the ones that are there, there's hundreds of hours of footage and like, you know, fun and...
No, just laughs and panic. There's so much like to it and it's like so I think I have been doing a good job on the show
Thank you
Okay, some money
Yeah, well, you know you that was like I think I think that was you're probably my most generous donator on the channel and
You know, I think you're really yeah, I'm not you know
I'm not gonna ever forget forget that and this you know what and it wasn't
It's enough that I'm gonna be able to buy a computer which is like I've been needing for so long
I was like I'm never gonna be able to afford it and get it as like I have a
Old one that kind of sucks and I don't want to use it
So it's gonna really really help. I have streamed every day. Yeah, and the brakes too like I'm when I go on tiktok
That's the rejuvenation too because it's like and then it keeps me more excited to go here
Because then it gets me all hyped to go here. Maybe so they'll come over there
Here from there and there's more it's just like I should be focusing on one
But I think I've put so much energy on the YouTube that it's like it's good
Just to like at least like not throw all it's like, you know, it will exhaust people if I just put all the energy into it
I mean I have a little bit a little split up so I can like, you know
Have a different kind of like energy change a little bit and then I'll it'll be a better move for here
I think right so
That's what I'm gonna try to do
I'm gonna be still planning on streaming every day here and I plan on as maybe six days a week on tiktok
Or seven days a week just doing
Just see me and want to join
He may have some of the
Was some of the richest one because they've been here for a long time
Do you want to join or are you feeling that you don't want? Yeah, let them join man. I will
Nobody's hopped up yet, but um anybody who wants a problem off like it
What I've got ghost doesn't bite. He just he's a little he'll tell us snap at you a little bit. Maybe yeah, no
He's yeah, that's true
But yeah, I was like it was yesterday was an interesting day like uh, it was like, you know, I was on last night
Well, I
But I went to bed brother
Yeah, I went to bed a little a little bit earlier last night. I had like a nice big macaroni and she's dinner and then like
You know
Brother why I thought I'd knock me out. I thought about I
Like Taco Bell well on tiktok. I did I was up for a little late
But yeah, I have got I have 800 and something followers there. So I'm almost at a thousand
Step two of monetization will be the thousand. I'm already monetized. They're basically with the membership program
It's just like, you know, it's a little bit of a harder sell than on on YouTube
It is I have a free trial for and a three dollars over there
And it's a little bit different than the YouTube one
But you know, take talk it and then Instagram to like Instagram files to do Instagram
I need 10,000 followers and plus to have the premium to be monetized on there guys
I'm also on x2 if you want to follow me on x. I'm psyche awakens on x
psyche awakens tarot on tiktok
I'm Psyche Awakens on Snapchat.
Huh, what?
Well, go ahead.
I'm so sorry.
Go ahead.
I was just telling you my links,
and also you can go to, guys,
you can go to chirpchirp.me
slash
Psyche Awakens and that is kind of like my has all my links are there
It's like a little bit of a landing page for the show
And so it's like if you ever need to like find my cash app or you can just like bookmark that page
I'm gonna I'm gonna put it basically in my name soon, but that for now. It's like a chirp.me
Slash Psyche Awakens also on my community wall. I have a link to it
under one of the logos and then you can
Check out check that out. It has all my links on it has my Amazon influencer page. It has my social media links and
You know to become a member and stuff like that and all kinds of stuff. So thank you guys
I hope you guys are having fun on the show though and I
Still love doing the show. I was but last night it was kind of quiet and I was like well
There's a lot of people that are now doing longer shows and you know, I just love running tonight
Yeah, I'm running it tonight. I'm down to but I'm down to play tonight. I got a couple beers tonight
I didn't I wasn't drinking last night. I got oh shit. Well. Hey, he man
You know first it's gonna come up here and she meant a shot straight up. He man talk to a lot of that
Join he man
Come on. He man. Come on up. You know meet us for the first time. You don't have to show your face
It's just be on give me for the free enough to pay. I'll literally pay for you just doing
Say what you're gonna say, right? It's not that fucking big of a deal. We're gonna hate on you
Well, you're gonna get nice hit and Boston Boston's the second dude that's gonna come up here
And let me tell you that they got three dudes the third dude that's gonna come up here is
Now I just want I'll take some I know you're gonna have fun with me
I'll take some of Jamie Q if you don't mind Jamie. Are you feeling okay? Yeah
I'll take some of Jamie. If you don't mind, sir. Okay. Well, Jamie, I know Jamie is still recovering from
Everybody come on. Come on guys. What are you waiting for guys? You know, we want to say hi to you
Uh, we got ghosts here wanting to talk. He's not a free panel. I paid for a paid for a free panel. They're gonna join really
They're going to I think I think I think they're just figuring out the stream yard. I don't want you to pay to join
No, no, no, no, don't pay don't pay anything. Well, if you want to pay yeah, play him 30 diamonds said
Yeah, I mean come on
Get on or whatever it is
Okay, flirty if you're there you're welcome to
Please please join
Okay, Jamie's gonna come up in ten minutes. She said okay ten minutes. We have ten minutes my ass
Come on. No, she'll be up. She'll come we'll be patient. No, I want somebody now, though
Okay, spunky. Are you there spunky can say hi ghost ghost is a cool dude
Spunky can I would love to speak to spunky, okay?
No
Well, I totally agreed. You know spunky is a doctor and very also a very sweet generous cut like a good hearted person
Okay
All right. Hey, it's like yeah, I'm hanging on ten minutes just for Jamie
But I guarantee it if they come over from this bullshit. I'm gonna fucking crash out. They're not Jamie
It's gonna be something good. I ain't hanging on the fucking ten minutes
Jamie and Jimmy just got out of the hospital. Okay, give her a second. She got out of the hospital. She got
All right, that's fair that is fair
All right, yeah
Guys, I have invited Myrna a couple of times on this show too, is bringing me out of the
depression.
Yeah.
I contacted Myrna, because she did post on my wall about Michael and stuff.
But did Jamie break her legs though? Can I ask that?
Jamie, well, I showed some of her pictures on the show, which she was in the hospital.
I wasn't no fucking picture.
Her hand was all bloody.
Jamie, can I, is it okay if I show that picture or not?
She's still on our RD.
What is RD? Rest in recovery? What's RD?
Still on red?
Um, she's still on research department. I'm not sure we're already stands for but already are our fucking I'll put this
Who wants to talk to me anybody can talk to ghost and arbiter goes
Anybody will put it off their psyche. My name's arbiter. My name's chris. Well ghost anybody that was talking if you have the chance now
Let's do it for the next 10 minutes. Let's do it
Anybody open okay, so so so Jamie and Boston are both gonna come up. They both said they're going to I know
Yeah, they are and I will get them I get them in the past. I'm talking about anybody else. Yes anybody else
Want you think about whatever they want. Yeah, anybody else. I'll show you but I'll show you I think Jamie said I can show the
picture of her in the hospital
And I'll do it wait. Do you want to see it? Oh, I'll show you hold on a second
You don't really want to see it. Well, I just want you guys to see that she was in a series
You'll see which I believe her. I'm trying to debate other people. I'd love to talk to her when she's which is here
Fuck it show it see it
Pretty crazy huh saw that yeah
Wow, I think God you're okay, Jamie. I mean that got a few oh, yeah, she oh, she had some x-rays. Yeah, so she
Yeah
But yeah, I think I take talk I've also you know, they have a tick tock store. I don't I am actually I bought something on there
I think a t-shirt or something like that for like that a $5 coupon no minimum that they let me use what cost me like $3 to buy
That should come soon
But I think I'm gonna get the computer on Amazon.
Okay, I was considering Tmoo,
but it's a little bit too much of a risk.
Like I can get a probably really good one.
It's either gonna be really good or really terrible
and I don't wanna take the risk,
but it'll be too hard to return there.
So I'm gonna find the best one on Amazon
or perhaps I'll see how much it will cost
to do a custom built gaming PC.
Because sometimes it's not too expensive.
There are some websites that like kind of like
have other people that are really to computers
I'm not, you know, I think I have a good, um, good price range, um, for, I really like
the, the computer to be able to do VR fine in it.
I want a gaming PC with VR that does streaming well.
That's all I need.
I mean, it's like, but the VR doesn't need a little, you know, good graphics card and
a good, uh, good RAM and stuff like that.
So we'll see, but I'm excited.
I'm excited.
It'll be, it'll be coming soon.
I'm going to set it up out here.
I'm going to make a little studio out here with my microphone up and everything.
I'm looking really forward to that also. I might get some other cool stuff just for the show and you know
I'll be able to get some stuff. I had this stuff. I need to I've been putting a lot of stuff off here, you know, you know because
You know, I mean it's been a little tight, but now I actually have some
Little little stuff to spend so I'm really excited. So thank you guys so much. We haven't done a coffee walk outside for a while
Yeah, well yesterday at Starbucks. I had a coupon for $3 coffee for a Starbucks any coffee for $3
So I went yesterday and use a coupon so today. I didn't get any coffee, but
Yesterday was
Okay, well, let's do it good ghost go ahead
No, you're fine. You're fine ghost ghost. They're gonna be up in a second. So just hang tight. Well, we're right there
I'm sure okay. Everyone's really looking forward to talking to you. It's just you know
People some people got scared off the panel some people are just like, you know, or just rude and it on and so they get mad
And so they haven't been back on it like, you know
Canada dry
Canada dry kicks. I kicked off the drive. He fucking he's up. I'll tell you I'll talk to him. He's a pussy
Well, I was you know, what I was I was I was listening to like I
Guess it was a beat his show maybe a month ago. It was like yeah by the month ago or less than a month
It's like three weeks ago and you know, she doesn't have he deletes her streams, right?
But they um, but she's syndicated somewhere. I'm not gonna give unless they want me to tell yeah
It doesn't move faster. That's why it's better for my readings my style reading, but uh, yeah
So yeah yesterday
I forgot what I was gonna say, but okay, so he man can't come up tonight, but second
It's really exciting that you are making money doing what you enjoy
I know and it's like the people and also but either people they don't believe it
And they say you oh, you can't make it or join. Yeah, they can yeah, they can talk
They can miss like they or else people are they get jealous and they're like, oh, why is he doing this?
Like why how why is he making money doing it?
It's like if you don't see like all the work I put into the show
It's like that's really update. That's really like your issue not mine
Because I worked hard on this show that I worked on any job in my life and any there's more hours
And it's like, yeah, it's fun most of the time and sometimes it's not fun. It's like sometimes it's hard work
And it's like and then I'm trying to go everywhere else trying to promote this show and bring people here
And I've done a pretty good job. This is why I wanted an open panel. I wanted more people to join
Nobody joined
Let's have on my part. Nobody joined
They're coming up. They're coming up. You have 20 people to chat and two people are on their way
Well
I will I know the two people like Jamie said a few minutes and then a Boston strong said a few minutes he man can't come up tonight
Spunky flirty diamonds or anybody else
Reality Nancy, I'd love you you come up sometime and say hi. I've never I'll be nice. I'll be nice
I know you will I heard but I've heard reality Nancy's voice. I talked to her on the phone before but I've never
talked to her on the show
But yeah, I think I think my show is pretty like
All right, like my show is like it's a 99 percentile for a lot of stuff like for example, I'm making more
Tips on tiktok than 99 percent of people with my same amount of followers and stuff
And so it's like I'm I'm able to I'm able to like do this for me
I think I'm being on YouTube for so long really got me into like
Being able to like yeah, I can now I can go over there instead of like just like if I started them all at the same time
It would have been too
Stretched to thin but now that I've really established this show and this shows established the show has very loyal people
You know, it's kind of slowed down a little bit in the growing the subscriptions and stuff like that
I've been like 20 over 2000 now. I'm at 2600 or 2300 or something like that
but and it's slowed down a little bit but
Think it's going at a good rate. There's there's always new people coming in. It's a little bit calmer here
Then it was but in a good way
Yes, oh, so ghost trolls by hitting bong so hard to the oh, I do
Sorry
Who does CD? Hold on. Who's CD?
Who's annoying you're saying let me see
I don't see you. I
Missed that but anyway
Got a lot of stuff on the works guys though, too. Also, my book is outlined, you know the the the troll book
That's outlined. It's gonna be a man. Yeah, he man if you're gonna run your mouth the fuck comments. Go ahead and join
Let's run that bitch. Oh
You're not gonna do nothing are you
Why you talk to somebody goes I don't like you talk to my friends here. She wants to talk or he did he wants to talk to you
I was talking to he man
They talked to my other friend hold on one second
Hello, are you there? Just any of you one of friends want to talk I don't mean to be disrespectful
We can be respectful brother. You don't appreciate the way I talk to your friends
Maybe your friends and come up here next to it and I think they want to talk to me here
Talk to anyone
Fuck you mean
Can you talk to my friend goes please see how do my friend goes friend or listen
No, join the pain listen to me you joined the panel
Guys you can't hear the person
No, I can't you can join the panel
Okay, I know I'm trying to get into here. Hold on a second. He's talking over. I'm gonna join the panel
I'm not gonna help you. I mean try again. Do you hear me now?
Just now you've got a pretty awesome friend over here trying to make sure you're okay. Hold on
Because this is a dark game. I'm sure I'm panel. Oh my god
Well, she can't the person's I think they don't have streamer to access hold on
Can you say hi to ghost, please
Absolutely, I'll give ghost a proper hello
Hey ghost, I'm not sure if you can hear me yet, but I'm definitely rooting for you to get everything sorted out
Whenever you do hear this, we're all here having a good time, and I'm always happy to say hi, isn't
All right, I'll keep it nice and straightforward
Ghost you're officially welcome to the conversation. You can
Yeah, I can hear I can hear is that a her I can hear you
Yes, trust eventually go now here all my enthusiasm
See if you say hi again
Of course one more time for good measure. I can hear you. Hi ghost whether you can hear me right?
Oh, no, just know you're definitely near you whenever the sound kicks in on your end
You'll have a whole collection of greetings waiting for you
Okay, I'm not really it's not
anything else you need me to do
or if ghost has any questions.
Don't have a question.
I didn't ask one.
I didn't make the claim, did I?
I don't have a question.
Nobody's making a claim.
Hold on a second.
I'm going to put it on a
Calm down goes. Hey one second sweet beach quite okay
Okay
Leave me go. I can hear you, but barely are you okay? Yeah, I'm putting her I'm putting her on a louder speakerphone
Hold on one second. Okay. I'm just fucked up. Okay. Well, I'm gonna see if she can hear me. Really psyche
Yeah, hold on a second. This one. This one. Yeah, I mean one second
One second, okay
Well, so it what it but what else is going on with you? Have you how was your day?
All right, it goes off you fucking
You're a piece of shit. Oh, you really try to do that to me. Who?
You you what what what are they saying?
What do you more do they say you're the one bringing them here what what I do?
Oh, here's random guy hold what I do tell me why my piece of shit goes why'd you say that?
I'm gonna ask you that question sweep you sweep you you're ruining everything you quiet
Okay, hold on. You don't stop ruining everything. Okay. How much money she gave me?
Zero okay. No, I'm just kidding. She's my first member. I appreciate her. Hello. Are you there?
Okay, here's our here's random guy talk to you. Hey, how you doing ghost? What's up? How's your day going?
Yeah, fuck you too, ghost
Anywho, um
You're an asshole
How am I not so I
Want to talk no more to you. I'm done with you. I'm talking so I'm talking to psych now
How am I not so you just made the claim to burden that person? I have to be on you. How am I not so I got time for this shit
You don't got then why the fuck would you even step up?
Exactly that's exactly so set there exactly up and reset money be quiet
Send him some money
He oh, yeah, yeah, you want more money. You want more money. I've said more. Are you all more money?
Yeah, you said it more money
Well, both of you are very generous donators. I love you both. So I hope you get along. Oh, yeah, dude
Listen, you owe me for a few months site
Would you like a few cards right now? No, I don't believe it. No, no, no
I'm sorry. Geez
Yeah, random guy you get you have a couple panels to come into you if you want to schedule a panel open to you can go
I don't know now though. Yeah, come into you because it's ghosts right now, but yeah, so you too
So who's this Zebs person ETC Zebs?
I think it's pebs it's pebs
Have yeah
Really cute girl. She's a really cute woman and she's really nice and she's a stream
She's a podcaster. I mean she's she has a stream. I know he pebs Joe. I was on a slurdy diamond before yeah, right?
So I knew about that stream because I'm you know pristine likes to
Broadcast pretty much all of your competition on your stream, which is nicer her
Anywho fucking um, I went over there
I tried, I sent five bucks, I said, give me a wrench, she didn't give me a fucking wrench.
And then I, you know, I wanted to say something in another super chat for two bucks.
And every word, every fucking word you try to say on a super chat is censored, highly
censored.
You can't even say booty.
You can even say B-O-O-T-Y in her super chat, and I told her about it, and some fucking guy plopped out of nowhere
Started riding my dick. He's like, oh, that's not my fault. That's YouTube's fault. You come on come to YouTube
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, like dude. No, you're fucking lying. Why are you so pissed off right now, dude?
You're fucking lying. I was like, no, you censored in your fucking stream dick head
And that's why you can't say it on the motherfucking super chat. Why do you think I'm stupid?
Didn't block words probably or they filter on yeah, exactly. He tried to gaslight my ass
You know what? I'm not sending a fucking penny over there ever again. He goes suck a dick that's that guy
Okay, yeah, well Zaya Zaya and peps
Zaya Zaya and peps
Yeah
She's really nice actually. She's really sweet and and actually so a lot of people like you know in the panel verse like
Basically, um, Tripp kick
Syndicate all the panel verse and so basically it's not that many people that are really considered like it
I mean, it's like so I mean the people that are syndicated are like good times me
Vita
Q45 I think maybe blogger some other people. Okay. Here's a Boston strong. It's coming up. Let's see how about Boston strong
I'm a second one second
Boston, your camera or your mic? Oh, here we go. Here. One second. Hello
What's up
How are you this is that you're on the air with with with the random guy and me I don't know where it goes to him
Fucked off. What are you watching at Boston golf?
What are you watching?
Hey Arbiter, thank you so much
Ghost that's ghosts. Yeah ghosts is Arbiter. Thank you so much for the super chat goes
Very sweet. Oh, okay. Here's a Boston strong fell off. Okay
Thank you ghost for that
And I'm good ghost. I also the soup of the
It's a called the cash app if you want to cash up is or instead or something like that in the future because
Sometimes that's easier to do so whatever you'd like to do, but thank you so much. Here's Boston strong is back here
We go. Yeah, so hello
This is your picture
Okay, love you. Hey, look at this guy. Okay, so are you so you're from Boston, right? Yeah
Do you want a cup of coffee? I don't know how you say it. Do you sound like the you sound like the Jersey Shore people?
Oh, here's here's goes back to talk to you. Okay. Oh now ran. Okay goes back my boss and fell off
Ghost
Now I was just I was on a quick rant. That's it. I mean there's no more to the story
I don't want to I want to overplay. It's it wasn't that interesting. You're fine
You know anything to ghost ghost is here and boss is strong here. You can say I try talking
It's he ignored me. He ignored me. So we can play games
You want to play games in front of the whole fucking internet, dude? You know, you can go fuck yourself ghost
I'm not doing it. I don't go so what's your argument? I can just go
That's that's that's a statement
it's not an argument. It's not
right. So, I'll just go fuck
myself then. Alright, have a
good night. Pretty much. Pretty
much. Alright, have a good
night. Thanks for your
argument. Have a good night.
Anybody else?
Boston's a hated ghost. Don't
go. So, how you doing? How
are you doing, Boston? Nice to
meet you, brother. How you
I'm just hanging in there.
Hanging in there.
You're singing in there?
Yeah.
Hey, man.
He sounds really excited.
Guys, wake up.
Have some energy.
Yeah, we're just mad.
Go, come on.
You're not allowed to talk anymore, sir.
Run that shit.
Well, you're like, you know what? I would actually pay two more if you'd actually run it
But you're fucking retarded to have it if you're being smart enough
I actually would let you run it sir. I would because I got I want
No, I think I'm riding a motor vehicle with it. I'm driving right now. I just I can't really perform. Okay
Who's talking? It's a is a random guy
I don't want random guy here
This fuck the guy
Are you sure yeah
Then guy, who are you?
I'm some random guy. That's literally who I am. All right, then I don't yeah, I'm sure I don't want him here
It's in the fucking name, dude
So pretty you have to pretend you have you have two wishes and you have one you have two wishes
So one of these wishes is to kick off random guy for 24 hours
I'll pay for three and that's one of the three, he's not here anymore, he's gone, he's gone, he's gone, he's gone
I'll see you later, random guy
Oh boy
You wish it was my command
Where is Canada dry when you eat them?
I don't know where he is, I haven't seen Canada dry in a little bit, ooh, hold on
Or J1
J1, Canada dry?
Come on up
I prefer Canada dry
I don't say
Good good
You guys do you guys like the cards I made so here I showed you the cards I made here's the
The lovers oh and that's not the lovers long this one's the lovers no show me the back of the card
Like that on the back of the car like well that these are these are the ones I'm making ghosts
These are the ones I'm making so it's like they'll be like what's the black and gold the back of them
I'm I well that was like the my my logo. I might put on like this. I have my logo right here
This is the logo right here you can see the top of the top left the top right of the screen
That's one of the logos, but this is mine. I have a new one too
That's that's spunky and Justin. Okay, and then I have
That's the one that okay, then I have the wheel of fortune. It goes into a couple like that's one of them
this is one of them and
You know who that is that's Emma and then this is one of them
I'm thinking about which one I want, but yeah, I think I like that one the best that that's pretty cool
Oh, by the way, it's like you can bring it back. Whoever the fuck you want. I was just kidding. You can bring it back
Okay, random guy if you want to come back up. You want to come back up random guy? You're welcome, you know
He like he's uh, he's he's he's uh
Giving you the pass on your on your I am giving them the pass. He's gonna take it or not
I don't know he might he might not he's like he might be insulted and have left
But I did listen to some beater today
It was funny because it was like I guess it was like Samann and
Eldo on the panel with like JT and
Other people and then like you know pie Rana was in the chat
You got like it's got like bombed by like somebody's swearing and stuff like that
Yep, it was pretty funny. I mean the
You know, I do like listening to it and you know, it's like she I think that was the time she was really mad at Kate or something
But hopefully a beat is doing good. I love you beta. Hey, Christine
You went to a chiropractor and you infuse sleeping
It's been a tough few weeks with trying to keep healthy. Oh, I hope you're feeling better Christine everyone send some love and
Love and good. You should join toast. Oh, she's rolling
Anyone come up here goes wasn't say hi to you Christian. Yeah, she's been hurting lately, man
are back. Yeah. I did. I did see Christine yesterday. I went I went to summers a few times
yesterday like I went last night and I said Christine was just finishing up there and
summer summer was having a good panel last night. Yeah. Yeah. Sweetheart. Love you Christine.
Sweetheart. Yep. Trix is doing good. Hey Trix you want to say hi to Ghost? I'm going
to wake you up and you want to say hi to Ghost?
You cut it with me in the morning. Oh, yeah, I gave him a flea treatment yesterday
And so you have no fleas and you're so happy you're like, oh all the fleas are gone. Oh
You had a flea treatment, huh? Oh
I mean, I'd rather say hello to Christine, but yeah, I'd rather say hello
Hi girls. Hi. How are you? I'm tricks. Hi
He's an eye. Oh, like you sound deaf word. I'm not gonna make the slur. You sound like an effort
She's a random guy you'll kick off and bring all on on all evening. Yeah, I get ready random guy
You're he's gonna he's about to change his mind again. I go goes changes of mine more the more than a woman changes her purse, but
But yeah, go we love ghosts and so I'll I'll give him a little I'll give him a little leeway
Today. Oh, hi, babe. I see a little fleasy on your chin chin chin. Okay. We're good. We're good. You're clean clean bill of health
No, no, I'm talking to you can't I'm talking to him. Oh, here's that easy easy wants to hide you ghost
Psyche, what up my guy? What's up? How are you? It goes but I'm ghost. How you doing?
Ghost
I just sent you his live. I didn't I didn't listen to the conversation
I just go goes keeps at he goes keeps wanting people to come up and then when they come up
He's starting stops talking. Why did you go silent goes?
Well, I'm here now goes. You already know easy in the building
You like easy go that boister strong. Oh, yeah
I haven't seen him since god knows
Look at ghost random guy finds you entertaining to be honest
Well, that's good, you know because uh because it goes that you can come back
I mean talking about you. I've gave you so much money. I've donated random guy
No, whatever you want goes
Talk to me what happened goes to sponsor in tonight. We are he
You heard shout out to go for sponsoring man. Good looking
At least one man was set there and say thank you. I mean goddamn I
Think you go I love you. Thank you so much for sponsoring the panel by the way. I love you
Hey, yeah, whoever supports support man. Yeah, I did my I did my I did my half I supported our support
Yeah, anyway, you want to support support, you know, it's funny that today there's this lady and and uh, like she has a channel called like
I hate Eli or something like that or something like that
And I was like and then she was like talking about little cows and then there's like lady named summer on her panel
Then she was talking to somebody named Jamie in the chat
I was like, do I know you guys and she's like and I was like, is this a fam Eli this blah blah and she's like
She's like, uh, no, it's a different one. And so it was a totally different one. It's just so random. It was so weird, but uh
I don't I don't know my brother. I'm sorry. Hey Vicky. Hey Vicky. How are you in chat Christine? Oh shout out to the chop
My ever seen the chat
Yeah, yeah, oh
Abel I mean fatal random guy Christine Vicky. Hey, what up everybody?
What up? Yeah, erby erby. Yeah, can I give you one dirt?
Yep
Okay, oh
You can go ahead and stairs easy. Can I give you one year?
Yeah, what happened what you need what you what you what you want to do?
Kick anyone for $25
Oh, you're gonna keep me. Hey,
I was reading the banner. I was
reading the banner. You got to
the wrong banner. Hold on. I'm
sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Don't go so happen. I was holding. I was hosting. Hey, hey, listen, I mean you don't want to see that you're
What the hell is that?
What the hell you put
What's the picture Boston, I don't what's that why you putting that picture of Boston
That's what I mean. It's crazy.
Oh, you all smoke a pack.
Let me just let me just smoke a pack.
I'm boy. I can't smoke it. I can't keep winning.
All right, my bad. I don't mean to be a dick.
Let me go to the chat now. Now I'm going to chat.
Yeah, we're smoking on. Yeah, we're smoking on.
Yeah, we wouldn't chat is up. It was loud. That picture was wild Boston. That was I'm I am part of the fucking chat
We don't know nothing. We know we're winning
Well, it was that it's something weird. I don't know what why'd you pick the picture up?
It was nothing
Well, why would you put that up though?
Yeah
It's just looking like a weird a faded picture of a what you call it
Put the picture up again, I'll judge it
No, I'll say psyche look
Boston you like it easier. No, but nobody said that psyche said it's ghost panel, which it's obviously psyches panel top scene
It's literally his panel, but since like you I mean ghost is here. We all said it was open
You guys are all welcome to be your psyche. Did I did I miss direct? Yeah, you're fine. Yeah
Yeah, and I always say it's free speech. We should all always be up here, right? Yeah
Okay, cool. Okay. Cool. All right. Let's fucking run that bitch then
Yes, everyone good. Yeah, I think I'm all good. We're doing good psyche. I got you dog. Let's run that bitch dog
Okay, that's no fucking open panel anybody that wants unless your porn vomit anybody wants it
Let's fucking have it. We're running
Being psyche by the man. I did my dude's name psyche. We'll run it with anyone. Let's run that bitch dog
Yes
It's free speech. Let's run it. All right. What do you want? All right, go ahead
No, I said I said you inviting anybody to a running session. So I don't want to run
I don't want to run. I'm tired those fucking running you're for you. What you're gonna do is you're gonna get your fucking ass knocked out
That's what you're gonna do. You're gonna be a good boy. But me and psyche. We the big dogs are in here here
Yeah, yeah, we did. We run the panel. What's gonna happen is a great guy's gonna be good boys
You're not gonna break to us and me on the psyche. We're gonna run the fucking panel. Oh
But I respect everybody's panel
You I'm talking to you talking to you. You're not talking to me in psych. You're not easy
And I you're talking to me and psyche you're doing a fucking me and psyche you're
Thank you. Cool. I thought it was like you. That's why I can't yeah. Yeah, it's like yeah school and I'm cool
Leave us alone
Goes I was here to talk to psyche
Well, you want to talk to Saiki? Go ahead and talk to Saiki.
Yeah, Saiki, what up with the reading, man? I haven't got one for you in a minute.
Okay, I think you will like mine. Go ahead.
I think you will like mine.
What you gonna talk to Saiki? I'll slap the fuck at you, boy, you heard?
Any new deck? Yeah, shut the fuck up.
Any new deck you got?
No, I'll slap the fuck at you, boy, you heard?
What you mean?
I'll slap the fuck. This is my panel. Saiki started from my panel.
This is obviously but he said I'm gonna wash my hands. I'm gonna wash my hands. I'll be back. Thank you
You ain't running nothing how much money you gave stop it stop it little boy fuck you
Yeah, you were talking but now I'm talking here. I came here talking easy way
easy fucking I'll slap the fuck out you that's why you gave him to talk to that easy guy
yes easy what's up
nah I gave him too much information bro
hold on stop crucible
determination I gave him too much money
shut the fuck up for one second crucible
this is ghost panel
come on bro
this is ghost panel you dumb fucks
oh he's not the fucker
he said he just left the room
this is ghost panel
You just left
When he comes back what he's going to say you're
You're not go sponsor tonight go sponsor the tonight
This right you know if you got if you gotta if you gotta talk to me through the back check as he won't shut up thing
I don't want you to leave. I want
Give him one minute
I don't want you guys to leave. I want us off. I want to be a kid. I bring up some controversy easy
So every time I see you on the panel. I'm like, wait, is that the guy stabs somebody I'm not trying to bring anything up
Is that happen?
What repeat we just allegedly yes, you allegedly yes, I said he stabbed somebody. Okay. That's interesting. Was it like you like
So what did he say on the panel that made you that pissed?
That was that was the one for you. Hey, hey psyche. Just said it's my panel. I can he literally just
Dude, I was running. No, he literally just said that though
So I can't work with you no more dude. I can't work
Saki, I'm the king of free
Maybe you just need to know how to talk to go. So I think goes. Yeah, you're probably fired. It's in my piano or not
Yes, it's a pat. You've sponsored it, but it's not all right free speech
If you're gonna give us free speech let people talk like yo, both the show
Empress panel you don't be on Brooklyn no more because he don't go live so you don't be over there or not the fuck you're talking about
But go ahead and talk good
Okay, let's talk
Don't know where she's from
Wow
Hey fuck you fuck what you heard. Let's run that bitch dog
Let's run that bitch dog
But I know both of them are on the red off the panel, so he be talking about psyching shit.
Yeah, he's just a real one.
He's a man up to my shit.
Unlike other people, they'd be like, no, I'm not fucking.
I'm like, yeah, you're a real one, easy.
I mean, you fucking straight up stab people.
Like, how real do you get?
Yeah, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about,
you're what do you do?
What are you talking about?
That's not the fuck out of a boy like you.
Who's a fucking gangster, man?
My bitch, you're that fucking kid.
You love me, you're sure you would.
Yeah, I would.
You want to see it?
You wouldn't want to see it?
Oh, no, I don't want to see that dude. That's gay.
No, you can show that to Scythe on the backstage bro.
I know you guys are weird shit.
You pay him all kinds of money.
You ain't no fucking good nothing.
I beat the fuck out of you.
You wouldn't.
Yo, random guy, what are you doing?
What are you doing crying with God the other day?
Bitch in the mouth of somebody else's pen?
I forgot what pen it was.
How about it on the side?
Man, shut the fuck up.
Why are you crying, dude?
I remember that I remember you was talking about somebody you was talking with God
That up I'm making an argument
Stupid you don't understand what's going on. He's drunk right now. He doesn't have fun. It's not fun. Yeah, you're
That's right. Make that argument
They
You like to suck some dick you like to lick some volume you like to spin on the day you like to use two hands
Fucking second. What the fuck is you talking to you boy? I slept the fuck out to your yard
Let's run that bitch dog fucking faggot you ain't gonna run it
You're gonna sit there and sit there and say nigga because you're a white
Let's run it fucking faggots. Let's run it
And I'll fucking
Over time don't do it one more time. Don't test me. Please don't say it again. I asked you not to say it
So I'm saying over
Thank you. That was fun. Thank you guys. That was funny. Yeah, that was funny. I had to mute up
What can I say you can say anything else
Maya!
I'm I'm ending the panel and you say one more time ghost. I'm I'm ending the panel
It came back to take all his that exaggeration so
You know, I had a you know week with my wife here, but she took a flight back. So, you know, it's time to be back online
But I got time don't
You guys live in different areas, or is she just like traveling for work or something as of now, you know, Florida, New York, you know
But yeah, I was originally living with her oh, she was living with me whatever the case
These are hey, uh, spunky. Did you break up with the adjusting guy?
Oh, I thought you guys were like
God
I
Mean she's a darker you'd be stupid not to well, she's a woman. Yeah, we don't know. Well, hello
Powerful women, you know how it goes
Yeah
Say what? Yeah, what? Yeah, what we don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Juck it in the back like easy shut the fuck up
All I hear is mumbling what?
You don't the fuck here talking about your two stick to have the conversation too much of a female you don't know
Alright explain to you
Would you look for drink before you do that? I might need to drink to understand you
Are you just too stupid to do it? I think I'd have to lower myself to like whatever level you'd want to be able to translate
Alright I got it!
Okay, I came on here to tell you to be nice. What's wrong with you? You're on your like man period or something. Yeah, suck my dick, bitch. Oh
No, no, thanks. I already picked my teeth today
That was quick too, I like that I was short
Dude, she's destroyed you ghost. Mm-hmm. You got destroyed. Yeah. Yeah, name one time
Yeah, like he's got like a like a pencil dick like the size of floss. That's yes, what she did to him
Instantly
Name one time how she destroyed me
He's
It's kids
You know the good supporters out here pay attention. I had to make sure anybody
Is the pins the pinder now?
Um, we've got Boston did brand new guy. Okay. Oh, okay. Let's go
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Tonight's gonna be a good good night. Got a feeling
Okay, I'll get it. I'll get it.
I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll
get it. I'll get it. I'll get it.
Can you can't hear what's up mumbling? It's like really
I usually keep my volume. You know, that's only reason I think
No, I just posted the link just now. I am paying attention. I just I take I say get some trash picking out the cat litter and stuff
So I just okay. I'll put you back up right now. Here you go, huh? It's making moves while we talk people
That's all he's doing moving around the house making you know
Hey, hey, Spunky. Hey easy
Hey, Boston, I have a question. I truly truly have a question
You have somebody because he pays money you're gonna let him sit up here and be racist and homophobic
You should know anybody
So you sell your soul you sell your soul
is what you know my soul my soul I gave him a little I gave him he doesn't
understand he understands we don't say the n or the f I told him and I didn't do it again
after I told him not to do it again I told him two or three times two or three times I would have
kicked him off if you said it again if you kid I would have kicked him off it would have
in my opinion you for money are selling
your morals, your ethics, your standards.
Well, I mean, I'm not even like, those words don't bother me.
The point of the word is the TOS.
They don't, they don't, but the point is-
They're not against TOS.
Whatever you did.
Like, they kind of are, because I read the TOS and it said
that you're not supposed to be hateful.
No hate speech and stuff like that.
I think it's probably, because they're hate speech in some ways.
Well-
I don't think he meant it like that, but I think that's why I don't like-
They don't think he meant it that way.
I mean he sounds completely drunk. I mean he sounds really drunk
Okay, so let's give excuses, you know, oh, he just murdered somebody
I still let's dig up. I feel like I feel like two point five
Sam and I say don't say it and I mean sometimes they do something they don't I never got in trouble for it
But it basically I just don't like the word personally. So I was like it's a personal thing
Don't say it. You know if you don't hear us, but he's not listening
He's taking a little break and I just want everyone to just behave. I said I say the rules
I don't want to kick people off, but if I if I have to I will you know, and I know and Christina's they got right nice words
I think they're ugly words person. I don't use they're very ugly words
And it's been one of the things on your channels for as long as you've had your channel
I know but it's like that's the people that come here
I mean from the projects and that's a word we use it consistently and I'm learning I'm not to use it on your panel
There should be no excuses for
Average white guy or whatever
Somebody who grew up in the projects not using it learning not to use it where it is is consistent
It's just somebody who lives in the suburbs where it's not used at all
Or send a white guy to the project to say it
Yeah, yeah, right now the ghost ghost a good day in New York City and downtown New York City in the Bronx
Probably never left his comfortable little town
Yeah, I mean it's a so people don't have like, you know, right? I mean, he doesn't have the right to say it
But I don't think like I don't think it's me using a racial context
But I still don't like it. It's like let me say f-a-g-g-o-t. It's not necessarily saying it when he says
How do you like a white guy stay and and says the word? What the hell do you call that?
He's just being dumb. He's being dumb. Okay. I don't call it. It's ignorant. It's ignorant. It's ignorant and yeah
But that's like he's displaying his ignorance and then it's like it gives people you people get to see you know
It's like, you know, so hopefully maybe other people can like pressure him into like not I can't control
Come out of people's mouths. I can just like, you know, see you're right
You cannot control it comes out of people's mouth, but you control your panel. Correct, correct
Yeah, I give money I give him chance. I get people chances though
I give everyone chances, you know, and it's like some people will break them and some people won't but I did apologize
It was offended. Oh, I'm very I you know, I'm very offended, especially
Knowing we have a lot of gay people in this community and he says the effort. I'm very offended
I mean, I was from like Denny's and some of the IP2 and IP2 is like well, they're they're very gay and on one level where they're like, you know
You're getting drunk and like by sucking each other off on the other level. They're saying that word a lot
And it's like so I mean what do I say is like, okay? Well, yeah, they say it
But it's like it's just that of ignorance that they're saying it's like there's really not the history that they don't get this
Some people are just kind of like out of it. I don't know
Well, so, you know when he was about to commit some murder because he's drunk just let him off
It's the way you say wrong you said
He's drunk every night. He's on the panel anytime he comes on a panel he's drunk
You're not me, right?
You're you're different drunk
You're you you're you're drunk. I can normally handle it. No we can we can straighten your ass out
There's a difference
Right
You do shit. I'm drinking right now to take a zip-off for that one
Shit
Oh shit, I was watching a movie and
First person to pop up with psyche I said damn I haven't been there in a minute. Let me say what up
I'm not even gonna pay attention link. Oh, thank
I was sleeping watching a movie and I'm pusing anyone and the dog the freaking dog decided
Jumped up and I didn't came up the conversation. I'm just kidding. Say hi to psyche and chill for a little bit
How's the dog doing Kristy has a little posse he's not the one who woke me up. It's my son's dog
my son
He is a
lab shepherd mix
Oh pretty. Yeah, I'm very pretty dog. Very. Oh, excuse me. I'm so sorry. I'm just like a big sip of a beautiful dog
but he decided he wanted out and
decides to come over and wakes me up like a
Well, you're a little long time. I can't do that to you. They come look at my nose to wake me up.
Well one night I was sleeping and I do not allow animals while my cat, but like Fawzi
doesn't get on furniture, doesn't get on beds, doesn't get on furniture, they don't
get on furniture.
And I sound asleep and a 60 pound dog decided to jump up in bed with me and freaked me out.
Like what the fuck.
My dog, my dog, she's always sleeping with me.
No.
They can't help it.
They say, if they would sit on the side of, if I told them no,
get down, they'll sit down on the side of the bed.
No.
Yeah
See I don't I don't I mean dogs a lot side and they get in the dirt
They bring that dirt inside and then they get on your bed and there's bacteria and
Well, if you're a good dog trainer, which we actually do is you out of it is out of two things
You put the dog shoes on or when you don't put the dog shoes on you take them upstairs and you wash they pause
You know something. No, you want to know the best thing to do don't let them on your bed
They close the bedroom door, I guess
He lays by the foot of the bed
On the floor
They want to come cuddle with you though
You know, we don't know no, I don't kiss my dogs. I don't
Oh, I'll take your baby and I'll rub his head in bed his belly
There's a video there's a video of a Lee at least like French kissing her dog. I think his name is pickle or foxy
Yeah, she has her mouth open and of her it is licking her lips inside of her mouth
Yeah, it's a myth that
Dogs do not have the cleanest mouth
that's why you might get infected or get some infection when they're licking you type of sh**
no they really have the dirtiest mouth
their mouths aren't clean
yeah you gotta brush them sh** like a human
yeah that's a deal
that's a myth that they say, you know, dogs have the cleanest mouth.
That's a myth.
Bless us.
That's actually got the plaque just like a rather human day.
If you like, you know,
if you're a person that just haven't brushed your teeth for months,
you see the plaque that builds in between those gaps and turn hard.
That's what dogs happen to.
So it is the same way.
Um, Joe, Joe, what's up?
Like I don't guys are shit.
Fucking Joe's up there.
What up, Joe?
What up Christine, what up Fongie, what up FBX, what up back?
Easy bro, I'm not gonna drop down.
I'm not gonna drop down too.
And before I do though, I just want to say it goes. Come on. Have respect for people. Yeah, thank you
Take it easy everybody. Spunky Joe turn this shit up and everybody else in the future
Christina I'll see you later
Everybody's leaving when I joined them
Oh, man, Joe, you scared everyone away.
Joe cleared her room out.
He cleared her room.
OK, it's OK.
But I still like you.
I'm still here, Joe.
You got to come in here and fart like that was your problem.
No, I thought it was honestly really cool. That's like he got his
Personal readings open $25 for a half an hour is a really good deal and I will be getting my reading very soon
I cannot wait to get my reading members from members all like increases up to an hour
Well, I know but I'm trying to I'm trying to do it reasonably
I'm trying to do like a reasonable price because it's like kind of a special right now and so if you know if you guys
Yeah, I should be charging more
$75 you're right now you're right clicking
But it will be a I've done a few of them before for people and it's like
You know the one-on-one over the phone or the video and they've gone really really well and people have enjoyed them
You know and so I think everybody will but you know, I can't I'm I'm just selling like I'm trying to sell myself
So I'll just I'll shut up about it, but you know, it is a good deal
Go ahead guys
How's a how's Joe doing? How have you been Joe?
I'm just chillin bro. I'm not talking too much, but it's nice to be up here with you in spunky. Nice to see you guys
Well, you're fine. You're absolutely fine
Yeah
Sponkeys are you doing good spunky like so you like that you like the the devil and the and the lovers cards that I kind of
Based off of you, but I'm gonna make it more look like more like you I mean
I'm gonna give chat PC to your picture
So it like you know instead of do you a little bit more accurately, but you know, it was a good rough draft of it
I think I like how it went. What do you think?
Yeah
There's sponkeys kind of like a piece of firewoods of me
She really gets my fire going
You're like match like charcoal because you're really
Who's that noise?
Pickup line that was a pickup line
Are you gonna pick me up?
Where that fire would come from because I love the show but log up your ass
That ain't a pick-up line. Come on. That's a pick-up. No
So you're embarrassing me
All right, I apologize
Thank you for let me know exhaust like it's good. Yeah, man
And I
Shit, I will be buying my $25 half an hour reading and I wouldn't every second of that half an hour
Yeah, okay. I'll give you the whole hour. I'll give you an hour. You're probably a member
Can you do it nude the only thing I'm a well, I'll do it in the speedo, but you know
Yes, exactly
They're fun when I don't get porn bombed
Have you had many of you done some monkey have you been and have you been you've been porn bombs already?
I've been porn bombed. Yeah, someone pretended to be Christine and then came up with her picture and then changed it to a
DICK and then um
They pretended to be Sam and I did it too.
So when that happens, you just ended and delete it?
I did, yeah.
You did two more now.
Yeah.
Smartest thing.
Yeah, I guess we just gotta start using that banner more,
you know, like, cause that made the camp
the environment.
I figured it out, you know, I'm still new, so.
Yeah.
I mean you can use them. I mean they have some of you stream yard
They have some um, you know just the overlay graphics or you can make you can put up your custom when you have a
And you have I'm I'm I'm plus why I can put out a custom one
But yeah, the custom one is good to put up to or if you ever do a trial and you're able to put it up
Then you can the cancel it will still be up there to use and stuff like that
Also, you can get it streamer for 25 bucks a month if you like cancel it then they'll offer you like 25 a bucks a month
For like things three to six months
Yeah
Pretty good deal. That's what I do. So that's a great deal. That's a great deal. Yeah, I'm gonna figure it out
I haven't been on it enough
You know yeah, I haven't gone through things in my life, and I think it's $25 if I really get a reading
It's like I think it could straighten me out a little bit
So I've actually looking forward to this
You think you need to be straightened out Joe? You're all right
I think I think when people do get when people do get a $25 reading
It is like I think they do have some kind of big question or concern like an epiphany. Yeah, no
Oh, it's almost like it's almost like it's almost like
personal
The personal, it's private, it's private over the phone or video, like a one-on-one kind of thing, so it's like nobody else to see it.
Oh, I'm going to want to say volume.
If I asked you a question during my reading, and then you get into an argument with me a month later,
you're not going to be like, oh, Joe asked me this gay question.
No, no, no, it's a private reading. You can ask any question.
They're also confidential, kind of, so I mean, I would not tell anybody what happened in a reading.
Confidentiality is all I know if spunky and Justin will break up and then so I can date him
Joe yes
Why that bit of lovers cook I'd have to I'd have to remake the lovers car with you Joe and it would just lose it's magic
Well, you can leave us and Jay on the tree
Yeah, I put yeah, I'll tell James. I'll put it in Jane Jane said or an SNJ. Yeah. Oh, no, so so be the right J
Just in the background just sighing. He's like, what the fuck?
Who do you think carved on the first place? It was like who's that snake under the tree? It's just Joe and his natural foam
We're just being silly Tim. You don't got to attack me
But it is done extremely
Well, what's on the show if they don't have like space on it. I don't want to buy it
49, she's a 49er.
It doesn't look nothing like this.
She's a huge 49er.
It's wobbly.
You cannot see the lights.
Like it's...
All right.
I don't like it.
We're going to ask you a question.
Do you think psyche does terrify readings?
He will do a half an hour reading for $25.
Is that not a fair deal?
Yes, yes.
Damn right, it's a fair deal.
It's a great deal.
And I'm gonna buy mine sir. I'll buy you one too Kim. I'll donate him 50 if I don't need your 50
Can you do me and Kim not the first that'd be it? That'd be a baby at least an hour. I'll give you an hour. Oh
You get an hour Kim you hear that? Damn. That's like a disc double discount
I mean, I can't even sit here and tell you about Kim for an hour. So I can't wait to hear this
I actually just want to donate to hear you talk about Kim for an hour actually. Okay, you can ask about her
I mean, I'm definitely willing to like talk about her too, but yeah, I know I am I think that the
People will actually get to see my
But I'm going to give you $50
And I want you to give Kim's reading for an hour because I know Kim and I'm not saying you'll be wrong
But I just can't wait to hear your reading for Kim because I know
Out of all the tarot card people I've seen on youtube
This is the real motherfucker. I've seen psych tell people things that they didn't even know about herself. That's how good this guy is
You understand what I'm saying? So I'm gonna pay him to read your card. Are you will you accept that camp?
Will you accept that? Okay? All right. There you go. It's like you got it
I'm gonna give you the 15 tomorrow or Friday this Friday when I get paid. I got it right now, but
Appreciate it. Yeah, I
Have a cash up whenever you're ready and I will schedule within 24 hours for both of you. I'd love to do that
I'd love to but also like I was saying like I
Territors are kind of like it's kind of like it maybe like on the same terms as like a bartender or a hairstylist where it's like if somebody
Has some shit to talk about they just want to like talking like you know good opinion
It gets like an opinion or have another person
Somebody it went down. This is like you're I glad you said hairstylist because you're right when somebody cuts your hair for so long
You kind of get comfortable with them
You don't want to go to a new person to cut your hair just like you don't want to go to a new person to tell me my future
Yeah
Hair carter is not a hairstylist I'm a guy buddy, but do I do my hair correct?
Yeah, you do Joe
Take a look at this like it. What do you think about that? Look at that right there. Thank you. Oh good
Joe are you
Treatments, you know alopecia. Where's your hair?
Like you you make me feel bad. I got it. I'm sorry. Oh my god, that wasn't in my future
How good he is
But guys, go out there.
Well, I love you Joe. Thank you so much
Why do you predict that earthquake the other day and I don't think I don't predict like natural stuff
I'm pretty natural stuff
But you know what because I don't I don't really make predictions as much as like look at the current energies past energies
And the best way to proceed
Well, I think I think God he just had inside information about that not like he didn't predict anything weird
It wasn't weird. He knew about it ahead of time because
He's in that little loop, so but
Okay, so if you know how close in a die you say how close it's gonna die. That's not a psychic
That's not a psychic. That's having inside information
I mean if this was the police that he went to saying that and then he can pull cool and died
They he'd be in jail right now because they'd be investigating him because they're like, okay
Well, don't really don't even know that as if he would have done it himself, right?
So that's the same reason like a lot of psychics don't like to work with the police because they'll be just accused that they solved the crime
right but I mean they have been they have been because the police are like okay well and I guess
maybe sometimes there was a psychic that did it but who knows I don't know um I'm sure there has
been such that kind of case but there have been psychic set of uh I actually like solved cases
in this interview but not Sylvia Brown though she was pretty uh pretty not uh the greatest uh psychic
That she was there
Break my heart because every time I read it she's fucked. Oh, he's gay. You know what I want to fuck is
Ivana punch over
Yeah, I like a bono though. You don't fuck it. I
Like her too
All right
Love you
You never turn your camera on so we actually didn't see you but good for saying good to see you
Love you spunky
That's funky the end
Well, it's a joke her name's not actually a bonnet retard
That bull I literally packed it. So it's not that fool. Give me that bowl. Let me show give me the ball
Yo, it's not that I'm either bowl. No, why can't you know you're wrong? Let me show like you the ball. Oh
Now you're tapping it out
That's all that's in there, Joe.
All right, then back it back up.
Doing too much.
Sorry about this, Saige.
I'm doing too much, according.
Yes, you're doing too much.
So what's your problem with Ivana because you talk about my friend Ivana
I wouldn't want to have that name. Why not?
It sounds like I want to call a thing about a bunch of her names. I bought oh, hello now
She's not like she has a phone call. Hello. Somebody's calling me the phone didn't even fucking ring the phone did not even
Then
Ain't gonna tell me good Lord take it outside if you got a phone call or get out of my room
You guys fighting I got a phone call too. Hello. Who is this?
Oh, I'm being a douche bag, you know what I want to punch you
No, I literally want to punch you
Wow, well guys well guys can you sleep not fight is we're trying to have a we're coming down. We're coming down
So it's still coming through the same numbers. I'm gonna mute it. I don't want her phone call to be out. Thank you
I mean, I don't I mean I want to listen in the phone call it sounded interesting, but you know, it's just a little bit chaotic right now guys
This game I'm giving you $50 for her hour long ratings like she needs it. She needs it man. He really does need it
Well, we'll do it. We'll do I can't wait
What's the new one?
The new deck or what was the new what? Oh the new deck. I have the new deck called the it's called the it's called the
says haters expose
Evil eye oracle cards. I also have a deck called this cats and spiders by Christina Ricci
I have one called the audacity deck and a few other ones that I haven't opened yet
So I have a lot of decks that can look through. I think you'll enjoy
Cheers up good times. Oh, you're not good times. Cheers up. It's like
What is
Okay
All right, oh, I think it was a phone call. I'm sorry. I thought you were talking to me
Ah, she called me she called me turn on camera shit. I'm about to get beat up
Or beat off what does it do?
But please don't tell me when she's not here
Thank you was that for me a joke that was funny if it was okay
I was yeah, sorry that was funny like I'm not thinking beat up right now
And you're like don't talk about beta to me. That was funny see every once in a while you do make it
That was honestly like legitimately funny every once in a while people up here make legitimately funny jokes
I'm legitimately a funny guy. I'm a comedian
You know what the
People are like, oh, I bonded didn't bail her boyfriend out of prison. I was like that's a funny joke
Hey, of course she did. I mean, that's that's how she meets her boy friends through pen pal letters
to
Hello
You're calling her for my weed now you're calling
That's how good my weed is buggy, but you mind about smoke a little bit
This one's for you psyche. This one's going out to you brother
Get my lighter
Are you gonna accept like he's one hour long care of card reading to you
But listen to me you cannot talk not right now. We're not going to do it
But you cannot talk over him like when he's telling you
You got to shut up for an hour. You got to shut up for one hour. You
Can actually do
And thank you
You can't do that. I can actually do that. I can shut up
You cannot be quiet for more than two seconds that alone watch it watch this who can't be quiet for two seconds
Boom right there. Yeah, and see you had to wait for the extra second because you want even two seconds
Mississippi one Mississippi
It's the second Mississippi done
You're still talking you're still moving here. I'm whispering. That's not the same
It is whispering talking chat chat put a whisper in the chat it whispered is whispering
No
Where's scum a we need him go J dogs, right? Scum a get in your wheelchair and join the stream you fucking mentally underdeveloped
Sorry, psyche
Those comes this guy that went blind and now he comes up and cusses everybody out and blocks us off. He's like a blind evil person
He's basically Stevie Wonder is Stevie Wonder was evil
I think you will be really stoked about the reading, so I think you'll like it.
I really do.
Now I'll help you out.
Oh, hello?
Hello?
I think we hung up.
Oh, is he still there?
Did you just hear what happened, psyche?
Oh
And I tell them about
Joe, can you hear me psyche?
Joe, can you hear me? I hear you
Joe are you there? Kim just got a call and it was like you got a call from the
western maryland
Oh
Petino facility
Oh, do you want to call from?
I'm just kidding Cam, but it was like your cousin. I'm not trying to- I'm not going to talk shit
I just start talking about the call Cam. Cam, can you hear me?
What?
Did you ban me? Me? No, you're right here.
I'm just waiting for Irby Irby right there Irby
Me
Irby for why
He deserves a little banning
No, he's a good guy. He's a good guy. No the other week. He was being so rude in your chat. I remember that
Sorry
No, he was he was being disgusting he was a nasty little nickel
Oh, you're gonna go into my kitchen and get it
My name ain't Joe by the way, she's using my fake name obviously
Thank you, Ken
For using my fake name
The last thing I need is like British playcoats to get my real name, you know what I mean?
You know how these streets are, you know how crazy these trolls are. They're fucking, they have nothing better to do but to attack us.
I know it's terrible sometimes, but you know what? It makes us stronger, I think.
What the hell did Spikey ever do to any of you? All he's ever been was positive.
And you're going to attack my gay friend? Go fuck yourselves.
For you attacked him you cowards you little coward bastards
Attack I bought in a punch you first. No like literally attack her first. Hello
Well, she's in a chat I don't think she really cares
She's not in chat. She actually got bored. It was like I'm out of here. Joe's here like I'm fucking out
Unless she blocked me and I can't see her. I don't think
Oh, I actually have an old name Fred dirt. So if you ever see Fred dirt with that just know with the gay red head
Thank you very much. I
Thought you were the day
Well, that was the joke dumbass the joke was that I was on and off and I was the gay redhead
So you didn't even get a joke psyche man. You got sexy hair on your head
It goes he goes to your brain your brain's the underdeveloped man. You're underdeveloped buddy. I was a little bit slow
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Well, I got me your dick's fully developed put your brain
Well, I mean, I think I don't think it's going very well today. I mean, it's like I might have to
What's up, Lassie? What's up lads from New York?
Lowly low lesbian running New York. Oh, yeah, run it. Let's eat
your old creep
Let's eat you're calling her a creep
No, no, I'm not I'm calling summer a creep because she's so damn sexy
Summer I need a little piece of you pronto. I'll take six wings and
A piece of summer on this side
So we make sure actually gay well not yet not yet random dog you got to wait random gay
I mean your name is random gay. They're called me gay, but your name is random gay
So I'm trying to talk around
I don't get a salute lesbian. I don't get no salute. Just Jamie. Sorry. Fuck this shit, man. This is rude
Hey, people's gonna give people salute that not me. This is actually hateful very hateful
Just evil
Like you ever made it eat like a really evil person like just actually evil
Like I mean, yes everyone since I'm sort of this show
Aw, thank you, Summer. See you at least. Summer gives me some love.
Not that lesbian from New York. Nope. Not a piece of love yet.
Thank you, Summer.
I would love to just read Summers breath tattoos all day long like summer as Bible versus tattooed owner tits
And I would just love to sit there with a magnifying glass and just read Summers tits all day
Well, I mean the magnifying glass, I mean, it's like it's like in large
Period like the end of the sense was their nipples like come on now that's
That'd be that'd be blasphemous
I'd say God don't you turn these kids into anything like you turn bread in the fish
Don't you dare turn some or in anything?
summer don't need to be changed
Is it was in the fish and the loaves or what right give me a favor don't you dare change a hair on summer's body because she's already perfect
Thank you Lord
I'm trying to overtaught me came
You're trying to talk loud in the kitchen to be rude
Kind of flirt with summer here
Oh, you don't sorry summer you had something you have some kind of paragraph on your tits
I just want to read whatever they are whatever it says it says some women are
Um, you know or in the fire is some some women are born in it or something
Oh, no, no, no, no, it's like read that comment that troop scoop boogie said and that's a great song boobs
Boogie
On him from mexican andy and I hate them I hate to admit it, but that is true. That is actually true
What did you do to Mexican Andy I?
Assaulted that piece of shit
Can you guys hear her conversation?
It's like one of you must offer them because if it's fucking rude she's trying to be on the phone call, but she's over talking up
No, you're doing too much Kim
You shut the fuck up good lord
Hello, are you there? I don't think he's gone. Wow guys, I mean, I don't know
Should I stick around what do I do now?
It's not going too well. Let me see. Let me just look at the screen. Let me see if I have my glasses and check out the
What are you guys saying to me? Let's see, Irby's good
Erby he's watching no one's banned him
Erby yeah, you're in the chat
Oh, he left
And it was Erby's phone. Okay, so no one banned in his summer
So weed makes Joe gay yeah
Shout out to Joe whose cheater whose chest are you looking at? I don't have Bible verses on my chest
I have a black widow and she has a quote on her neck
It says, Joe has a sexual charm, okay?
And then it says, Joe, give Mexican Andy a titty twister.
Are you giving up on us?
You seem like to talk, I'm not giving up on you.
I'm saying, I mean, some are, it's been crazy.
It's because people, like sometimes in the chat,
have been so rude to me.
Like the past few days, I've had on, hold on.
I've had on, what's his name?
His name is Joe.
Okay, now who's the guy Tommy James and he's been so rude to me and like he said everyone hates me and like he's like
We hate you and stuff like or we don't like you
Don't you talk about oh, I will I will I will you're friends with him your friends
I'm not gonna kick you off. It's okay. You can be friends with them. He's just a dick. He's like he looks like
Like some character from Mr. Rogers that got like, you know kicked up out of the neighborhood and then he like tried to tell me
I'm bad. I don't know. He looks like
He belongs on a registry more than I do
You guys might as well be paying each other's nails right now like seriously every time Joe comes on it gets super gay
And he even like complimented your dick
It happens every time you take a toka that we do don't go ahead. Don't say a word. Hey, literally
You're saying it is making me gay. Yes
What happened what happened is like Joe started reading like, you know, how to win friends and influence people
By like Gil Carnegie and then he read like it was supposed to like, you know, compliment them and like
Pretend to be interested what they're interested in so he just became gay so we can relate to me better
But you know, I get it, but he doesn't really
Joe wants to experiment
Yeah
Well, this guy just said every time we agree with this guy random gay he said every time I smoke weed I get gay
Is that true every time you?
My house right now get the hell out of here. You're gonna pay that in front of random gay
No, he's like every time jokes go sweet.
Yeah, I did.
It's my fucking pack.
No, you gave it to me, dummy.
Okay.
Oh, hey, now you're going to take one out of my loop.
Look at this.
Look at her open in my new pack if I can show it.
Rippy, my pack of cigarettes open.
What are you going to do with them?
You going to take one?
So I'll go ahead.
What are you going to do with them?
Joe
Yeah, shut the fuck up listen me for a sec. Did you ever see her young black boyfriend?
Listen to me. Did you ever see her young black boyfriend cuz she put an avatar up above him?
Have you ever seen him?
Think she's lying
Says she speaks heavy heavy white trash
Heavy white trash accent I don't understand her
Why we can't stand you nigga, who the fuck can't you say?
He started we can't say the word daddy are you serious lucky we can't say gay come on. Are you kidding me? Come on site
Be safe. He really ended it cuz I said gang fuck you. I apologize
Drop a Nigel's Joe every time you come on
Which I
If it doesn't make it any better you're white
You don't get a fucking past you're not black
Like if you're not black
You fuck you
We're in the bag it
Hey, so did you hear him say he's dropping f's too?